http://www.ehappylife.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of eHappyLife.com and eHappyLife, LLC. If you do not agree to the Policy, please do not use this site. EHappyLife.com reviews its privacy policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. This page should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. If you want to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at joe@ehappylife.com
Cookies
eHappyLife, which operates the Internet site located at www.ehappylife.com, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our site. When signing up for membership, we ask for nominal information about members such as name, e-mail address, company and title. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information beyond this is asked for or collected from visitors to our sites.
Use and Security
Personally identifiable information that visitors submit to our site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Such other uses may include sending you an e-mail announcement containing information or materials we think you will find interesting.
Links to Third Party Sites
eHappyLife provides links to what we believe are reputable websites. This allows our visitors to conveniently and quickly navigate to other sites. eHappyLife is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to or from our site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by eHappyLife of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you have left the eHappyLife site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.
©2020 eHappyLife, LLC
Privacy Policy | Terms of use
